<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!--Know it - First Main Activity-->
    <string-array name="item_picture">
        <item>@drawable/first_aerial</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_crane</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_firesprinkler</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_forlift</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_heat</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_ladder</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_respiratory</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_scaffolds</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item_title">
        <item>Aerial Lift</item>
        <item>Crane Lift</item>
        <item>Fire Sprinkler</item>
        <item>Fork Lift</item>
        <item>Heat Stress</item>
        <item>Ladder</item>
        <item>Respiratory Protection</item>
        <item>Scaffoldings</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Know it - Second Activity -->
    <string-array name="second_desc">

        <item>Aerial lifts are commonly used in construction, inspection, athletic events and repair services to lift University employees to an elevated work position. Proper operation and use of aerial lifts can make completion of tasks at elevation, safer and more efficient. However, unsafe use, operation and aerial lift work practices can result in serious injury. This program has been developed due to the hazards associated with improper use and the concern for the safety of individuals in and around this type of equipment. In addition, this program outlines general, operating, maintenance, inspection and training requirements governing safe aerial lift use.
\n\nDefinitions:
\nAerial Device:  Any vehicle mounted or a self propelled device that is telescoping extensible, articulating, or both, and is primarily designed to position personnel.
\nAL / EWP: Acronym for “Aerial Lift/Elevating Work Platform”
\nBoom: An elevating member, the lower end of which is so attached to a rotating or non-rotating base that permits elevation of the free end in the vertical plane.
\nCounter Weight: The rear section or area of the lift which is usually made of solid steel, and/or combination of steel and the weight of the battery on electric lifts, that counter balances the boom leverage and basket load.
\nData Plate: Manufacturer‟s equipment specification and information data, which includes basket load rating/lift capacity, lift heights, vehicle weight, and vehicle attachments. This plate is required to be affixed to all Aerial Lift Equipment by regulatory code. This is the vehicle operator‟s primary source of basic information about their vehicle for safe-work and use planning.
\nEmergency Lowering Means: Any elevating work platform equipped with a powered elevating assembly, and having a platform height exceeding 60 inches, must be supplied with safe means of lowering the basket or platform during an emergency or malfunction.
\nFall Protection: An approved full-body safety harness with lanyard is to be worn at all times and attached to a secure anchor point when drivers or personnel are using a boom-type lift or vehicle mounted lift. Fall protection must also be worn when using scissor lifts on uneven surfaces or near locations with tip-over hazards.
\nGuard Rails: Railing around the perimeter of the work platform. This railing consists of a top rail between 39” – 45” with a mid-rail. Units with the top rail less than 39” must have fall protection in use to operate.
\nLower Controls: Operating controls located on the base of the unit which can be switched to override the basket or platform control during an emergency.
\nMast: Part of the lifting mechanism to which the hydraulic lift cylinder or worm drive is attached that supports the basket as it is lifted up and down.
\nOut Riggers: Extendable legs that are either manually set in place or, in some cases, hydraulically extended to give added stability to the unit base.
\nPlatform: Any personnel carrying device (bucket, basket, cage, stand, tub, or equivalent) which is a component of an aerial device.
\nUpper Controls: Operating controls located on the basket or work platform of the unit. These controls can only be overridden with the operator‟s permission or in case of an emergency.
</item>
        <item>A crane is a tower or derrick that is equipped with cables and pulleys that are used to lift and lower material. They are commonly used in the construction industry and in the manufacturing of heavy equipment. Cranes for construction are normally temporary structures, either fixed to the ground or mounted on a purpose built vehicle.
\nThey can either be controlled from an operator in a cab that travels along with the crane, by a push button pendant control station, or by radio type controls. The crane operator is ultimately responsible for the safety of the crews and the crane.
\nTower cranes are used extensively in construction and other industry to hoist and move materials. There are many types of tower cranes. Although they are different in type, the main parts are the same, as follows:
\n•	Mast: the main supporting tower of the crane. It is made of steel trussed sections that are connected together during installation.
\n•	Slewing unit: the slewing unit sits at the top of the mast. This is the engine that enables the crane to rotate.
\n•	Operating cabin: the operating cabin sits just above the slewing unit. It contains the operating controls.
\n•	Jib: the jib, or operating arm, extends horizontally from the crane. A "luffing" jib is able to move up and down; a fixed jib has a rolling trolley that runs along the underside to move goods horizontally.
\n•	Counter jib: holds counterweights, hoist motor, hoist drum and the electronics.[41]
\n•	Hoist unit: the hoist unit houses the hoist drum, hoist cable, gear box, gear shift, brake, and supporting components.
\n•	Hook: the hook (or hooks) is used to connect the material to the crane. It hangs at the end of thick steel cables that run along the jib to the motor.
\n•	Weights: Large concrete counterweights are mounted toward the rear of the mast, to compensate for the weight of the goods lifted
</item>
        <item>A fire sprinkler or sprinkler head is the component of a fire sprinkler system that discharges water when the effects of a fire have been detected, such as when a predetermined temperature has been exceeded. Fire sprinklers are extensively used worldwide, with over 40 million sprinkler heads fitted each year. In buildings protected by properly designed and maintained fire sprinklers, over 99% of fires were controlled by fire sprinklers alone.
        \n\n
        Parts of a sprinkler system
\n•	OSY- Outside Stem and Yoke
\n•	PIV- Post Indicator Valve
\n•	Main Control Valve- Controls water for whole system
\n•	Main Drain- Drains System
\n•	Inspector Test- Tests system
\n•	Alarms- Waterflow or Air Alarms
</item>
        <item>A forklift is also known as a lift truck essentially because it’s a truck that can lift loads using a set of forks. A forklift can be used in numerous places such as warehouses, factories, farms, shipping yards and much more. There are many types of forklifts which can be called a variety of different names; in this case we will use the basic names of the forklifts when describing their capabilities.
\n\n
	•	Mast: The mast is the vertical support that permits raising and lowering the load.
	\n•	Carriage: A support structure where the forks are attached or mounted.
\n	•	Back Rest: Attached to the carriage and prevents the load shifting backwards, it protects the mast cylinders hoses as well as preventing any goods falling through the mast and hitting the operator.
\n	•	Fork (Tynes): The cantilevered arms attached to the load carriage, that engage the load.
\n	•	Lift Cylinder: Controls the amount by which the mast structure, forks and carriage may be raised or lowered in the vertical.
\n	•	Overhead Guard: A framework/roof, providing overhead protection for the operator from falling objects.
\n	•	Tilt Cylinder: Controls the amount by which the mast structure, forks and carriage may be tilted beyond the vertical position, forward or backward.
\n	•	Rating Plate: This is used to inform users of the maximum load a forklift can legally carry.
\n	•	Counter Weight: The weight installed by the manufacturer to give stability to the machine under load.
</item>
        <item>Workers at risk of heat stress include outdoor workers and workers in hot environments such as firefighters, bakery workers, farmers, construction workers, miners, boiler room workers, factory workers, and others. Workers at greater risk of heat stress include those who are 65 years of age or older, are overweight, have heart disease or high blood pressure, or take medications that may be affected by extreme heat resulting in heat stress.
\n\nPrevention of heat stress in workers is important. Employers should provide training to workers so they understand what heat stress is, how it affects their health and safety, and how it can be prevented.
</item>
        <item>Ladders are used when employees need to move up or down between two different levels. Slips, trips, and falls are significant contributors to accidents. Slips, trips, and falls can occur when wrong ladder selection is made and when improper climbing techniques and/or defective ladders are used.
\n\nAppropriate ladders must be used for the corresponding job and defective ladders will not be used. When hazards exist that cannot be eliminated, then engineering practices, administrative practices, safe work practices, Personal Protective Equipment (PPE), and proper training regarding ladders must be implemented.
</item>
        <item>Respirators protect workers against insufficient oxygen environments, harmful dusts, fogs, smokes, mists, gases, vapors, and sprays. These hazards may cause cancer, lung impairment, diseases, or death. Compliance with the OSHA Respiratory Protection Standard could avert hundreds of deaths and thousands of illnesses annually.
\n\nRespirators protect the user in two basic ways. The first is by the removal of contaminants from the air. Respirators of this type include particulate respirators, which filter out airborne particles, and air-purifying respirators with cartridges/canisters which filter out chemicals and gases. Other respirators protect by supplying clean respirable air from another source. Respirators that fall into this category include airline respirators, which use compressed air from a remote source, and self-contained breathing apparatus (SCBA), which include their own air supply.
</item>
        <item>A scaffold is a temporary structure specifically erected to support access or working platforms. Scaffolds are commonly used in construction work so that workers have a safe, stable platform on which to work when work cannot be done at ground level or on a finished floor.
\n\nScaffolds, once properly erected, are a control measure to prevent the risk of persons and objects falling when working at height.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="second_safety_rules">
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item> ●	All wood parts must be free from sharp edges and splinters; sound and free from accepted visual inspection from shake, wane, compression failures, decay, or other irregularities.\n
\n●	Ladders must be maintained in good condition at all times, the joint between the steps and side rails must be tight, all hardware and fittings securely attached, and the movable parts shall operate freely without binding or undue play.\n
\n●	Metal bearings of locks, wheels, pulleys, etc., shall be frequently lubricated.\n
\n●	Ladders must be inspected frequently and those which have developed defects must be withdrawn from service for repair or destruction and tagged or marked as "Dangerous, Do Not Use." \n
\n●	Ladders with broken or missing steps, rungs, or cleats, broken side rails, or other faulty equipment shall not be used; improvised repairs are not allowed.\n
</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>Work at Height Regulations 2005
\nWork at height is defined in regulations as: Work in any place, including a place at, above or below ground level, where a person could be injured if they fall from that place.
\nExample: Work below ground level could be work at height if for instance a large pit has been evacuated and someone may fall either from an unprotected edge or whilst descending into that pit.
\nWork at height regulations apply everywhere, in all industries and in every activity at height, where there is a risk of fall liable to cause personal injury.
\n\n
Who has duties?
\nAccording to the work at height regulations the following are considered duty holders: Employers, self-employed people, employees and anyone else who conducts or controls work at height activities.
\nAll duty holders must avoid working at height where they can, prevent falls where they cannot avoid working at height, protect from the consequences of a fall where they cannot prevent fall.
\nSo, all duty holders must
\nAvoid 
\nPrevent 
\nProtect
\n\n
Working at Height Regulations – Overriding Principle
\nThe overriding principle which applies to all work at height is that you must do all that is reasonably practicable to prevent anyone from falling.  
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="second_types_image">
        <item>@drawable/second_aerial</item>
        <item>@drawable/second_cranelift</item>
        <item>@drawable/second_firesprinkler</item>
        <item>@drawable/second_forlift</item>
        <item>@drawable/second_heatstroke</item>
        <item>@drawable/second_ladders</item>
        <item>@drawable/second_respiratory</item>
        <item>@drawable/second_scaffolds</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="second_image">
        <item>@drawable/first_aerial</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_crane</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_firesprinkler</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_forlift</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_heat</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_ladder</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_respiratory</item>
        <item>@drawable/first_scaffolds</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--Know it - Third Activity-->
    <!--Title-->

    <string-array name = "aerial_lift_title">
        <item>Articulating Boom Lift</item>
        <item>Elevating Work Platform</item>
        <item>Extensible Boom Platform</item>
        <item>Scissor Lift</item>
        <item>Trailer Mounted Lift</item>
        <item>Vehicle Mounted Lift</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="crane_lift_title">
        <item>Mobile Cranes</item>
        <item>Telescopic Crane</item>
        <item>Tower Crane</item>
        <item>Truck Mounted Crane</item>
        <item>Rough Terrain Crane</item>
        <item>Loader Crane</item>
        <item>Overhead Crane</item>
        <item>Truck Mounted variable boom</item>
        <item>Crawler Mounted variable boom</item>
        <item>Gantry crane</item>
        <item>Jib crane</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fire_sprinklers_title">
        <item>Wet Sprinkler System</item>
        <item>Dry Sprinkler System</item>
        <item>Deluge Sprinkler System</item>
        <item>Pre-Actions System</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fork_lift_title">
        <item>Industrial Reach Forklift Trucks</item>
        <item>Industrial Counterbalance Forklifts</item>
        <item>Rough Terrain Forklifts</item>
        <item>Industrial Side Loader Forklifts</item>
        <item>Telescopic Handler Forklifts</item>
        <item>Pedestrian Operated Pallet Trucks</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="heat_stress_title">
        <item>Heat Stroke</item>
        <item>Heat Exhaustion</item>
        <item>Heat Cramps</item>
        <item>Transient Heat Fatigue</item>
        <item>Fainting</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ladders_title">
        <item>Step ladder</item>
        <item>Extension Ladder</item>
        <item>Portable Ladder</item>
        <item>Trestle Ladder</item>
        <item>Mobile Ladder</item>
        <item>Articulated Ladder</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="respiratory_protection_title">
        <item>Disposable Particulate Respirators</item>
        <item>Half-Mask Replaceable Particulate Filter Respirator</item>
        <item>Full Face piece Replaceable Particulate Filter Respirator</item>
        <item>Tight-Fitting PAPR</item>
        <item>Loose Fitting PAPR</item>
        <item>Fixed Air Supply</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="scaffoldings_title">
        <item>Supported Scaffold</item>
        <item>Frame or Fabricated</item>
        <item>Mobile</item>
        <item>Pump Jack</item>
        <item>Tube and Coupler</item>
        <item>Ladder Jack</item>
        <item>Pole or Wood Pole</item>
        <item>Cantenary Scaffold</item>
        <item>Interior Hung</item>
        <item>Multi-point Adjustable</item>
        <item>Single-point Adjustable</item>
        <item>Float (ship)</item>
        <item>Multi-level</item>
        <item>Needle Beam</item>
        <item>Two-point (swing stage)</item>
        <item>Vertical Ladder Towers</item>
        <item>Inclined Ladder Span Towers</item>
        <item>Frame Access Towers</item>
        <item>Stairway or Stairway Ladder</item>

    </string-array>

    <array name="third_title">
        <item>@array/aerial_lift_title</item>
        <item>@array/crane_lift_title</item>
        <item>@array/fire_sprinklers_title</item>
        <item>@array/fork_lift_title</item>
        <item>@array/heat_stress_title</item>
        <item>@array/ladders_title</item>
        <item>@array/respiratory_protection_title</item>
        <item>@array/scaffoldings_title</item>
    </array>



    <!--Description-->
    <string-array name="aerial_lift_desc">
        <item>An aerial device with two or more hinged boom sections.
An articulating boom lift is a type of crane that uses hydraulic cylinders to rise and lower and allows a driver to maneuver the boom in any given direction directly from the work platform without lowering the basket. The articulating boom lift is specifically made with at least two boom sections that are hinged and it unhinges at certain points, this makes reaching higher elevations easier.
\nArticulating boom lifts typically operate with an electric motor or internal combustion as their powers source. It can not only rotate 360 degrees, but also access spots higher than most straight or telescoping boom lifts. They are narrow enough to be maneuvered easily through aisles and crowded work areas and are often found being used in construction, landscaping and plant maintenance.</item>
        <item>A device designed to elevate a platform in a substantially vertical axis. This device is stationary once setup and cannot be moved. Aerial or Personnel lift is an aerial lift that combines the portability of a ladder with the stability of an aerial work platform.

\nSimple to set up and easy to roll through doorways with a rigid vertical mast and leveling jack that offer stability for the user, the vertical mast raises the work platform to the desired height. Reaching heights of 47 feet and lifting up to 300 lbs, these personnel lifts are more stable than a ladder. It is ideal for indoor use and is suitable for fragile surfaces.
\n\nNote: Fall Protection is not required when operating this equipment, but is highly recommended.
</item>
        <item>An aerial device (except ladders) with an extensible boom. Telescopic booms with personnel platform attachments are considered to be extensible boom platforms. If you are looking for a boom lift with an extended reach capability then a telescopic boom lift is right for you\n
        Operable from the work platform, even when extended, some telescopic boom lifts are equipped with a jib that provides extra reach and range. Reaching up to 140 and offering a greater horizontal outreach than any other type of aerial platform, these boom lifts are often used in construction and industrial applications such as road building, bridge work, painting, and landscaping.\n\n
        Note: Fall Protection is required when operating this equipment.</item>
        <item>A device designed to elevate a platform in a substantially vertical axis. This device can also be driven by an operator inside the work platform and is generally designed to carry more than one person.
\nAlso known as a table lift, a scissor lift is an industrial lift that has been modified for retail and wholesale setting. Powered by hydraulics, diesel or an electric motor, this lift will reach anywhere from 21 to 62 feet. It is basically a platform with wheels that acts like a forklift.Portable and effective, this is a lift is useful for completing tasks which require speed and mobility.

\nThe scissor lift is unique in that it doesn\'t use a straight support to raise workers into the air, instead, the scissor lift platform raises when the linked, folding supports underneath it draw together, stretching it upward. The scissor lifts design keeps it from traveling with a constant speed, instead traveling faster in the middle of its climb and slower as it elevates. It can be seen in nearly all manufacturing and production workplaces, including construction, assembly, and vehicle repair.
\n\nNote: Fall Protection is not required when operating this Lift, but is highly recommended.
</item>
        <item>A device that can be towed by a vehicle to a work site, then un-hitched. These units have extendable or folding outriggers to give stability while being operated. These are compact cranes that can lift up to 30,000 lbs. Designed for both indoor and outdoor job sites, these lifts feature telescoping booms and a load deck for material handling.

\nThey are made for the work place and are self propelled, usually capable of picking up a load and traveling with it. The crane is equipped with a flat deck that is designed to be used as a carrying surface they are perfect for lifting applications requiring a compact, low-profile crane that will clear overhead obstructions and maneuver in tight spaces.
\n\nNote: Fall Protection is required when operating this Lift.
</item>
        <item>These devices typically have a Bucket in place of a basket, which is designed for one person. Vehicle must have the brakes set, wheels chocked, and outriggers in place while operating this device. Also  Frequently used by contractors due to their lightweight structure and maneuverability, they are ideal for congested job sites.

\nAs the name states, tow able boom lifts are tow able, easily transportable and ready to use in minutes. Easy to maintain due to having less parts,they are easy to break down. Most have an articulating boom, but some models have a telescopic arm. They are light weight enough to use on lawns, slate, or gymnasium floors and are perfect for home renovations and property management needs.
\n\nNote: Fall Protection is required when operating this Lift
</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="crane_lift_desc">
        <item>The most basic type of crane consists of a steel truss or telescopic boom mounted on a mobile platform, which could be a rail, wheeled, or even on a cat truck. The boom is hinged at the bottom and can be either raised or lowered by cables or hydraulic cylinders.</item>
        <item>This type of crane offers a boom that consists of a number of tubes fitted one inside of the other. A hydraulic mechanism extends or retracts the tubes to increase or decrease the length of the boom.</item>
        <item>The tower crane is a modern form of a balance crane. When fixed to the ground, tower cranes will often give the best combination of height and lifting capacity and are also used when constructing tall buildings.</item>
        <item>Cranes mounted on a rubber tire truck will provide great mobility. Outriggers that extend vertically or horizontally are used to level and stabilize the crane during hoisting.</item>
        <item>A crane that is mounted on an undercarriage with four rubber tires, designed for operations off road. The outriggers extend vertically and horizontally to level and stabilize the crane when hoisting. These types of cranes are single engine machines where the same engine is used for powering the undercarriage as it is for powering the crane. In these types of cranes, the engine is normally mounted in the undercarriage rather than in the upper portion.

</item>
        <item>A loader crane is a hydraulically powered articulated arm fitted to a trailer, used to load equipment onto a trailer. The numerous sections can be folded into a small space when the crane isn’t in use.</item>
        <item>Also referred to as a suspended crane, this type is normally used in a factory, with some of them being able to lift very heavy loads. The hoist is set on a trolley which will move in one direction along one or two beams, which move at angles to that direction along elevated or ground level tracks, often mounted along the side of an assembly area.</item>
        <item>A crane mounted on a truck carrier provides the mobility for this type of crane. This crane has two parts: the carrier, often referred to as the Lower, and the lifting component which includes the boom, referred to as the Upper. These are mated together through a turntable, allowing the upper to swing from side to side. These modern hydraulic truck cranes are usually single-engine machines, with the same engine powering the undercarriage and the crane. The upper is usually powered via hydraulics run through the turntable from the pump mounted on the lower. In older model designs of hydraulic truck cranes, there were two engines. One in the lower pulled the crane down the road and ran a hydraulic pump for the outriggers and jacks. The one in the upper ran the upper through a hydraulic pump of its own. </item>
        <item>A crawler is a crane mounted on an undercarriage with a set of tracks (also called crawlers) that provide stability and mobility. Crawler cranes range in lifting capacity from about 40 to 3,500 short tons (35.7 to 3,125.0 long tons; 36.3 to 3,175.1 t).
\nCrawler cranes have both advantages and disadvantages depending on their use. Their main advantage is that they can move around on site and perform each lift with little set-up, since the crane is stable on its tracks with no outriggers. Caterpillar tracks are also far better at traversing soft ground without sinking in, as they spread the weight out over a great area. Thus a crawler crane can move about an unprepared job site with less risk of getting stuck in soft ground. In addition, a crawler crane is capable of traveling with a load. The main disadvantage is that they are very heavy, and cannot easily be moved from one job site to another without significant expense. Typically a large crawler must be disassembled and moved by trucks, rail cars or ships to its next location.
</item>
        <item>A gantry crane has a hoist in a fixed machinery house or on a trolley that runs horizontally along rails, usually fitted on a single beam (mono-girder) or two beams (twin-girder). The crane frame is supported on a gantry system with equalized beams and wheels that run on the gantry rail, usually perpendicular to the trolley travel direction. These cranes come in all sizes, and some can move very heavy loads, particularly the extremely large examples used in shipyards or industrial installations. A special version is the container crane (or "Portainer" crane, named by the first manufacturer), designed for loading and unloading ship-borne containers at a port.</item>
        <item>A jib crane is a type of crane where a horizontal member (jib or boom), supporting a moveable hoist, is fixed to a wall or to a floor-mounted pillar. Jib cranes are used in industrial premises and on military vehicles. The jib may swing through an arc, to give additional lateral movement, or be fixed. Similar cranes, often known simply as hoists, were fitted on the top floor of warehouse buildings to enable goods to be lifted to all floors.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fire_sprinklers_desc">
        <item> •	Water is in branch lines and at the sprinkler heads at all times\n
•	Wet Systems cannot be in areas that may freeze\n
•	Water pressure must be maintained at all times \n
•	Water Pumps are put in place to keep water pressure at a certain PSI \n
•	There is no delay in time that water is put on the fire \n
•	Require the least amount of maintenance
</item>
        <item>•	Require Air Pressure instead of water in the Branch Lines
\n•	The Air Pressure holds down a Clapper Valve, so that water can not be introduced into the system, unless the air pressure is lost
\n•	Used in areas that may freeze
\n•	An air compressor keeps a constant pressure in the system
\n•	When a Fire releases a sprinkler head, the air is released from the piping, and stops holding down the valve that was holding the water back, and water is released


\n•	Standpipes are used in stairwells to have a water way established for hand lines
\n•	These systems have a high maintenance cost, due to corrosion in the pipe with only air, and a little bit of water
\n•	Might take up to 60 seconds to get water on the fire, depending on how big the system is
</item>
        <item>•	Deluge Valves are used in special areas
\n•	Sprinkler heads are open at all times
\n•	Used in High Hazard areas
\n•	Deluge Valve opens during a smoke or heat detection
\n•	Deluge systems are needed where high velocity suppression is necessary to prevent fire spread.
</item>
        <item>•	Same as a Dry System
\n•	Water is held back by an electronically operated valve
\n•	Two things need to happen before water is released
\n•	The detection system must identify that there is a problem with smoke or flame
\n•	Water is then released into the piping
\n•	Secondly the sprinkler heads must be activated and released to put water on the fire.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fork_lift_desc">
        <item>•	They are renowned for their extended lift height, making them ideal in any warehousing situation with high rise storage pallet racking.

\n•	There are different types of reach forklift truck that are best suited to a range of scenarios:
\n-	Stand-up trucks are the most common and are often used where there’s only one load per bay. The two forks on the front of the truck slide underneath palletised loads, to lift and transport safely.

\n-	Double-deep trucks are similar, but with longer forks, making them perfect for areas where multiple pallet loads are stored in each bay as they will reach right to the back of the bay.

</item>
        <item>•	Industrial counterbalance forklifts are the most common trucks used in indoor warehouses and stores, although they can be used outdoors, on stable, even surfaces.

\n•	They offer straightforward operation and have dual forks at the front of the truck that lift and transport the loads.

\n•	There are different types available, including three-wheel models that provide better manoeuvrability, making them perfect for narrow aisles.
</item>
        <item>•	For outdoor construction and with difficult terrain, a rough terrain forklift is ideal.

\n•	It has inflatable tyres with thicker threads, allowing stability on uneven ground, as well as a more powerful engine so it can reach higher speeds, and better manoeuvrability, making them must more robust and durable.

\n•	This means that they are perfect for transporting heavy loads across rugged terrain, with some models handling up to 3 tonnes per load.
</item>
        <item>•	Side loader forklift trucks are ideally suited to working in narrow aisles.

\n•	This is because the forks are mounted to the side of the truck and can pick up wide or long loads that would be awkward or inaccessible with a straight forward forklift.
\n•	There are two main types of side loader forklifts
\n-	The enclosed cab that is most commonly used outdoors, and a stand up version that is more suited to indoor tasks.

\n-	The other type is the multi-way version, where the wheels all rotate by 90°, allowing ease of transportation in any direction.As a result, they are especially useful for lifting and transporting tubing, pipes and sheet materials safely and efficiently.
</item>
        <item>•	Telescopic handler forklifts are ideal for use in agriculture and all kinds of industry that require high lifting.

\n•	They offer a whole range of features that make them much more useful in a range of situations, so much so that they are often thought of as small cranes, rather than forklift trucks.

\n•	Telescopic handlers have the additional advantageof a single telescopic boom that allows the truck to become a much more powerful and flexible piece of machinery.

\n•	There are a number of practical attachments available, including a lift table, bucket, pallet fork and muck grabber.
</item>
        <item>•	Pedestrian operated lift trucks and pallet trucks are most commonly used in warehouses and storage facilities for the easy transportation of pallets.

\n•	All pedestrian operated trucks have forks that slide beneath the pallet and use a hydraulic jack to lift the load from the ground for easy manoeuvrability.

\n•	There’s a wide variety of styles and designs available, some capable of moving loads of 5000lbs, but the main difference is between the lift and pallet trucks.

\n•	The pallet truck is simply for moving loads from one place to another at ground level, but it has limited reach, while the lift truck is more complex and is capable of transporting and lifting a palletised load onto a higher level or for stacking loads on top of each other.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="heat_stress_desc">
        <item>Heat stroke is the most serious of health problems associated with working in hot environments. It occurs when the bodys temperature regulatory system fails and sweating becomes inadequate. The bodys only effective means of removing excess heat is compromised with little warning to the victim that a crisis stage has been reached.
\nA heat stroke victims skin is hot, usually dry, red or spotted. Body temperature is usually 105_F or higher, and the victim is mentally confused, delirious, perhaps in convulsions, or unconscious. Unless the victim receives quick and appropriate treatment, death can occur. Any person with signs or symptoms of heat stroke requires immediate hospitalization. However, first aid should be immediately administered.
</item>
        <item>Heat exhaustion includes several clinical disorders having symptoms which may resemble the early symptoms of heat stroke. Heat exhaustion is caused by the loss of large amounts of fluid by sweating, sometimes with excessive loss of salt.
\nA worker suffering from heat exhaustion still sweats but experiences extreme weakness or fatigue, giddiness, nausea, or headache. In more serious cases, the victim may vomit or lose consciousness. The skin is clammy and moist, the complexion is pale or flushed, and the body temperature is normal or only slightly elevated.In most cases, treatment involves having the victim rest in a cool place and drink plenty of liquids.
</item>
        <item>Heat cramps are painful spasms of the muscles that occur among those who sweat profusely in heat, drink large quantities of water, but do not adequately replace the bodys salt loss. The drinking of large quantities of water tends to dilute the bodys fluids, while the body continues to lose salt. Shortly thereafter, the low salt level in the muscles causes painful cramps. </item>
        <item>Transient heat fatigue refers to the temporary state of discomfort and mental or psychological strain arising from prolonged heat exposure. Workers unaccustomed to the heat are particularly susceptible and can suffer, to varying degrees, a decline in task performance, coordination, alertness, and vigilance. The severity of transient heat fatigue will be lessened by a period of gradual adjustment to the hot environment (heat acclimatization).</item>
        <item>A worker who is not accustomed to hot environments and who stands erect and immobile in the heat may faint. With enlarged blood vessels in the skin and in the lower part of the body due to the bodys attempts to control internal temperature, blood may pool there rather than return to the heart to be pumped to the brain. Upon lying down, the worker should soon recover. By moving around, and thereby preventing blood from pooling, the patient can prevent further fainting. Heat Rash Heat rash, also known as prickly heat, is likely to occur in hot, humid environments where sweat is not easily removed from the surface of the skin by evaporation and the skin remains wet most of the time. The sweat ducts become plugged, and a skin rash soon appears. When the rash is extensive or when it is complicated by infection, prickly heat can be very uncomfortable and may reduce a workers performance. The worker can prevent this condition by resting in a cool place part of each day and by regularly bathing and drying the skin.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ladders_desc">
        <item>•	Flat steps, hinged back
\n•	Use on firm level footing
\n•	Metal, wood, fiberglass
\n•	One worker
\n•	Metal spreader or locking arms
\n•	No work from top step
\n•	20 feet maximum length
</item>
        <item>●	Two or more sections
\n●	Upper section on top
\n●	Minimum section overlap
\n●	Wood, metal, fiberglass
\n●	One person
</item>
        <item>●	Single portable ladder
\n●	Slip-resistant feet
\n●	30 foot maximum length
\n●	One worker
\n●	  Wood, metal, fiberglass
</item>
        <item>●	Self-supporting portable ladder,
\n●	Non adjustable in length,
\n●	Consists of two sections hinged at the top to form equal angles with the base.
\n●	 The size is designated by the length of the side rails measured along the front edge.
</item>
        <item>A Mobile Ladder Stand Platform is a movable, fixed height, self-supporting unit having one or more standing levels and is provided with a means of access or egress to the platform or platforms. The assembly may include handrails and/or guardrails, and may be designed to accommodate one or more persons.</item>
        <item>An Articulated Ladder is a portable ladder with one or more pairs of locking hinges which allow the ladder to be set up in several configurations such as a single or extension ladder, with or without a stand-off, a stepladder, a trestle ladder, scaffold or work table. Each pair of articulated joints in the ladder can be locked in one or more positions to accommodate the various configurations. The locking positions of the hinges allow set-up at the proper angles to accommodate each configuration that the manufacturer has designated.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="respiratory_protection_desc">
        <item>The NIOSH-certified disposable respirators labeled N, R, or P and may be obtained with or without exhalation valves. Most manufacturers also produce them in different sizes. A face shield may also be used in conjunction with a half-mask disposable respirator for protection against airborne flying material and fluids.
\n\nAdvantages:
\n1. The respirator is disposable and most models require no cleaning or maintenance.
\n2. The respirator is light weight and fairly comfortable to wear.
\n\nDisadvantages:
\n1. The respirator is a negative-pressure device using the suction produced by inhalation to draw air through the filter. The inhalation process, even under the best of circumstances, will allow some contaminated air to leak into the face piece.
\n2. A respirator with exhalation valves cannot be used when working in a clean room/sterile environments. The exhalation valve allows droplets and particles exhaled by the user to escape and potentially contaminate the work area. These respirators are also available without exhalation valves.
</item>
        <item>This respirator has single or dual filters made of the same material as the N, R, and P disposable respirators (HEPA filters can also be used). Most manufacturers produce more than one size. A face shield may also be used in conjunction with a half-mask particulate filter respirator.
\n\nAdvantages:
\nA. The respirator is lightweight and does not restrict mobility.
\nB. The respirator is made of rubber or elastomer and is durable. Only the filters need to be replaced when necessary.
\n\nDisadvantages:
\n1. The respirator must be routinely inspected, cleaned, disinfected, and repaired.
\n2. The respirator is a negative-pressure device using the suction produced by inhalation to draw air through the filter. The inhalation process, even under the best of circumstances, will allow some contaminated air to leak into the face piece.
\n3. Communication may be difficult.
\n4. The respirator cannot be used in areas where a clean or sterile field is required.
</item>
        <item>The respirator can be equipped with the N, R, or P filters (HEPA filters can also be used). It is also manufactured in more than one size.
\n\nAdvantages:
\n1. The respirator provides a better seal than the half-mask and with HEPA or 100 series filter is more protective.
\n2. The respirator is durable.
\n3. The respirator provides eye protection.
\n\nDisadvantages:
\n1. The respirator cannot be used in areas where a sterile field is required.
\n2. The respirator must be inspected, cleaned, and repaired.
\n3. The respirator is a negative-pressure device using the suction produced by inhalation to draw air through the filter. The inhalation process, even under the best of circumstances, will allow some contaminated air to leak into the facepiece.
\n4. Communication may be difficult.
\n5. Special lens kits are required for those respirator users who wear glasses.
</item>
        <item>Equipment is battery operated, consists of a half or full face piece, breathing tube, battery-operated blower, and particulate filters (HEPA only). A PAPR uses a blower to pass contaminated air through a HEPA filter, which removes the contaminant and supplies purified air to a face piece. A PAPR is not a true positive-pressure device because it can be over-breathed when inhaling.
        \n\nAdvantages:
\n1. The respirator is more protective than a half-mask respirator.
\n2. The respirator is usually more comfortable because air is forced into the mask by the blower, producing a cooling effect.
\n3. The respirator is durable.
\n4. Breathing resistance is lower.
\n\nDisadvantages:
\n1. The respirator cannot be used where a clean or sterile field is required because it has an exhalation valve and in some cases air can exit around the face seal.
\n2. Batteries must be recharged and maintained to assure proper flow rates into the mask.
\n3. The respirator must be inspected, cleaned, and repaired.
\n4. Communication may be a problem.
\n5. A PAPR may be bulky and noisy.
</item>
        <item>This respirator consists of a hood or helmet, breathing tube, battery-operated blower, and HEPA filters.
\n\n        Advantages:
\n1. More protective than a half-mask respirator.
\n2. The respirator is more comfortable because it is loose-fitting.
\n3. Provides a cooling effect in the hood or helmet.
\n4. The respirator is durable.
\n5. Breathing resistance is lower.
\n6. Vision may be better.
\n7. Can be worn with facial hair as long as facial hair does not interfere with valve or function of the respirator.
\n\nDisadvantages:
\n1. The equipment cannot be used where a sterile field must be maintained because air exits around the hood or helmet.
\n2. Batteries must be charged and maintained.
\n3. The respirator must be inspected, cleaned, and repaired.4. Communication may be difficult.5. A PAPR may be bulky and noisy.
</item>
        <item>Supplied-air respirators use compressed air from a stationary source delivered through a hose under pressure to a half-mask or a full face piece. A face shield may also be used in conjunction with a half-mask airline respirator for protection against body fluids.
\n\nAdvantages:
\n1. The respirator is much more protective because it provides positive pressure in the face piece and almost all leakage is outward. A positive-pressure supplied-air respirator should be used when disposable respirators, replaceable respirators, or PAPRs do not provide adequate protection.
\n2. Breathing resistance is minimal.
\n3. The respirator is relatively comfortable to wear.
\n\nDisadvantages:
\n1. The airline hose restricts the users mobility.
\n2. This respirator exhausts air contaminated by the user and should not be worn during clean or sterile procedures.
\n3. The respirator must be inspected, cleaned, and repaired.
\n4. Communication may be difficult.
\n5. Requires installation and maintenance of a regulated compressed air supply for Grade D breathing air.
\n6. Maintenance requires highly skilled, technically trained personnel.
\n7. Length of hose and connection point must be adequate to prevent exposure to airborne contaminates when removing the respirator
</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="scaffoldings_desc">
        <item>Supported scaffolds consist of one or more platforms supported by outrigger beams, brackets, poles, legs, uprights, posts, frames, or similar rigid support. Because frame scaffolds are the most common type of supported scaffold. 
</item>
        <item>The most common type of scaffold because they are versatile, economical, and easy to use.
\nThey are frequently used in one or two tiers by residential contractors, painters, etc., but their modular frames can also be stacked several stories high for use on large-scale construction jobs.
</item>
        <item>Mobile scaffolds are a type of supported scaffold set on wheels or casters
\nThey are designed to be easily moved and are commonly used for things like painting and plastering, where workers must frequently change position.
\nScaffolds must be plumb, level, and squared.All brace connections must be secured.
\nTo prevent movement of the scaffold while it is being used in a stationary position, scaffold casters and wheels must be locked with positive wheel locks 
\nPlatforms must not extend beyond the base supports of the scaffold, unless stability is ensured by outrigger frames Leveling of the scaffold, where necessary, must be achieved by the use of screw jacks.
</item>
        <item>Pump jacks are a uniquely designed scaffold consisting of a platform supported by move able brackets on vertical poles.
\nThe brackets are designed to be raised and lowered in a manner similar to an automobile jack.
\nPump jack brackets, braces, and accessories must be fabricated from metal plates and angles.
\nEach pump jack bracket must have two positive gripping mechanisms to prevent any failure or slippage. When bracing already installed has to be removed so the pump jack can pass, an additional brace must be installed approximately 4 feet above the original brace before it is removed.
\nThe additional brace must be left in place until the pump jack has been moved and the original brace reinstalled.
</item>
        <item>Tube and coupler scaffolds are so-named because they are built from tubing connected by coupling devices.
\nDue to their strength, they are frequently used where heavy loads need to be carried, or where multiple platforms must reach several stories high. 
 \nTheir versatility, which enables them to be assembled in multiple directions in a variety of settings, also makes them hard to build correctly.
\nWhen platforms are being moved to the next level, the existing platform must be left undisturbed until the new bearers have been set in place. Braced before receiving the new platform.
\nThe use of couplers made from gray cast iron is prohibited. Tube and coupler scaffolds over 125 feet in height must be designed by a registered professional engineer
</item>
        <item>A ladder jack scaffold is a simple device consisting of a platform resting on brackets attached to a ladder.
\nLadder jacks are primarily used in light applications because of their portability and cost effectiveness. 
\nAll ladders used to support ladder jack scaffolds must comply with-Stairways and Ladders.
\n Ladder jacks must be designed and constructed to bear on the side rails and ladder rungs. Ladders used to support ladder jack scaffolds must be placed to prevent slipping fastened to prevent slipping and or equipped with devices to prevent slipping.
</item>
        <item>Pole scaffolds are a type of supported scaffold in which every structural component, from uprights to braces to platforms, is made of wood. 
\nOSHA has standards for two kinds: single-pole, which are supported on their interior side by a structure or wall, and double-pole, which are supported by double uprights independent of any structure.
\nWhen platforms are moved to the next level, the existing platform must be left undisturbed until the new bearers have been set in place and braced. Pole scaffolds over 60 feet in height must be designed by a registered professional engineer.
</item>
        <item>A catenary scaffold is a scaffold consisting of a platform supported by two essentially horizontal and parallel ropes attached to structural members of a building or other structure.
\nPlatforms supported by wire rope must have hook-shaped stops on each of the platform to prevent them from slipping off the wire ropes. These hooks must be positioned so that they prevent the platform from falling if one of the horizontal wire ropes breaks.
\nWire ropes must not be over-tightened to the point that a scaffold load will overstress them. Wire ropes must be continuous and without splices between anchors.Each employee on a catenary scaffold must be protected by a personal fall-arrest system.
</item>
        <item>An interior hung suspension scaffold consists of a platform suspended from the ceiling or roof structure by fixed-length supports.
\nInterior hung scaffolds must be suspended from roof structures (e.g., ceiling beams).
\nRoof structures must be inspected for strength before scaffolds are erected.Suspension ropes/cables must be connected to overhead supports by shackles, clips, thimbles, or equivalent means.
</item>
        <item>A multi-point adjustable scaffold consists of a platform (or platforms) suspended by more than two ropes from overhead supports and equipped with means to raise and lower the platform(s) to desired work levels.
\nMulti-point adjustable scaffolds must be suspended from metal outriggers,brackets,wire rope slings,hooks or means that meet equivalent criteria for strength, durability, etc.
\nWhen two or more scaffolds are used they must not be bridged together unless design allows them to be connected,bridge connections are articulated and hoists are properly sized.
</item>
        <item>A single-point adjustable scaffold consists of a platform suspended by one rope from an overhead support and equipped with means to permit the movement of the platform to desired work levels. 
\nThe most common among these is the scaffold used by window washers to clean the outside of a skyscraper (also known as a boatswains chair).
\nThe supporting rope between the scaffold and the suspension device must be kept vertical unless designed by a qualified person, accessible to rescuers, protected from rubbing during direction changes.
</item>
        <item>A float, or ship, scaffold is a suspension scaffold consisting of a braced platform resting on two parallel bearers and hung from overhead supports by ropes of fixed length.
\nPlatforms must be supported by and securely fastened to a minimum of two bearers extending at least 6 inches beyond the platform on both sides.open connections must not allow the platform to shift or slip.
\nWhen only two ropes are used with each float Ropes must be arranged to provide four ends that are securely fastened to overhead supports and Each employee on a float (ship) scaffold must be protected by a personal fall-arrest system.
</item>
        <item>A multi-level scaffold is a two-point or multi-point adjustable suspension scaffold with a series of platforms at various levels resting on common stirrups.
\nMulti-level suspended scaffolds must be equipped with additional independent support lines that are equal in number to the number of points supported,equal in strength to the suspension ropes and rigged to support the scaffold if the suspension ropes fail.
\nIndependent support lines and suspension ropes must not be anchored to the same points. Supports for platforms must be attached directly to support stirrups (not to other platforms).
</item>
        <item>This simple type of scaffold consists of a platform suspended from needle beams, usually attached on one end to a permanent structural member. 
\nScaffold support beams must be installed on edge.Ropes or hangers must be used for supports. Ropes must be securely attached to needle beams.
\nSupport connections must be arranged to prevent the needle beam from rolling or becoming displaced.Platform units must be attached by bolts or equivalent means. Cleats and overhang are not considered adequate means of attachment.

</item>
        <item>Two-point adjustable suspension scaffolds, also known as swing-stage scaffolds, are perhaps the most common type of suspended scaffold. 
\nHung by ropes or cables connected to stirrups at each end of the platform, they are typically used by window washers on skyscrapers, but play a prominent role in high-rise construction as well. 
\nThe safe use of a suspended scaffold begins with secure anchorage. 
\nThe weight of the scaffold and its occupants must be supported by both the structure to which it is attached and by each of the scaffold components that make up the anchorage system.
\nAdjustable suspension scaffolds are designed to be raised and lowered while occupied by workers and materials, and must be capable of bearing their load whether stationary or in motion.
</item>
        <item>Vertical Ladder towers
 \nOften referred to as span towers, and are generally available in two widths- single and double width.
\nSpan towers come in a variety of lengths: 1.5m-1.8m, 2.5m, 3m, 3.2m
</item>
        <item>They are often referred to as span towers, and are generally available in two widths=Single and double widths.
\nThey come in variety of lengths: 1.5m-1.8m, 2.5m, 3m, 3.2m
</item>
        <item>They are often referred to as span towers, and are generally available in two widths=Single and double widths.
\nThey come in variety of lengths: 1.5m-1.8m, 2.5m, 3m, 3.2m

</item>
        <item>Stairway towers are otherwise known as Stairladder towers
\nStairway towers are usually available in double width only.
\nAvailable length-1.5m to 1.8m
</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="third_description">
        <item>@array/aerial_lift_desc</item>
        <item>@array/crane_lift_desc</item>
        <item>@array/fire_sprinklers_desc</item>
        <item>@array/fork_lift_desc</item>
        <item>@array/heat_stress_desc</item>
        <item>@array/ladders_desc</item>
        <item>@array/respiratory_protection_desc</item>
        <item>@array/scaffoldings_desc</item>
    </array>


    <!--Image-->

    <string-array name="aerial_lift_image">
        <item>@drawable/third_aerial_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_aerial_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_aerial_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_aerial_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_aerial_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_aerial_6</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="crane_lift_image">
        <item>@drawable/third_crane_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_crane_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_crane_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_crane_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_crane_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_crane_6</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_crane_7</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_crane_8</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_crane_9</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_crane_10</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_crane_11</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fire_sprinklers_image">
        <item>@drawable/third_fire_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_fire_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_fire_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_fire_4</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fork_lift_image">
        <item>@drawable/third_forklift_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_forklift_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_forklift_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_forklift_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_forklift_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_forklift_6</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="heat_stress_image">
        <item>@drawable/third_heat_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_heat_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_heat_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_heat_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_heat_5</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ladders_image">
        <item>@drawable/third_ladder_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_ladder_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_ladder_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_ladder_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_ladder_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_ladder_6</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="respiratory_protection_image">
        <item>@drawable/third_respiratory_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_respiratory_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_respiratory_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_respiratory_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_respiratory_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_respiratory_6</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="scaffoldings_image">
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_6</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_7</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_8</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_9</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_10</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_11</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_12</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_13</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_14</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_15</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_16</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_17</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_18</item>
        <item>@drawable/third_scaffold_19</item>
    </string-array>


    <array name="third_image">
        <item>@array/aerial_lift_image</item>
        <item>@array/crane_lift_image</item>
        <item>@array/fire_sprinklers_image</item>
        <item>@array/fork_lift_image</item>
        <item>@array/heat_stress_image</item>
        <item>@array/ladders_image</item>
        <item>@array/respiratory_protection_image</item>
        <item>@array/scaffoldings_image</item>
    </array>


    <!--Know it - Fourth Activity-->
    <!--How to-->
    <string-array name="aerial_lift_howto">
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="crane_lift_howto">
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fire_sprinklers_howto">
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fork_lift_howto">
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="heat_stress_howto">
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ladders_howto">
        <item>●	Use a stepladder that is about 1 m (3 ft) shorter than the highest point you have to reach. This gives a wider, more stable base and places shelf at a convenient working height.
\n●	Open the stepladder spreaders and shelf fully.
\n●	Check stability. Ensure that all ladder feet are on a firm, level and non-slippery surface.
\n●	Place a stepladder at right angles to the work, with either the front or back of the steps facing the work.
\n●	Keep the stepladder close to the work.

\n●	Avoid pushing or pulling stepladders from the side. Repeated sideways movement can make ladders wobbly since they are weaker or less stable in those directions.
\n●	Face the stepladder when climbing up or down. Keep your body centered between side rails. You have climbed too high if your knees are above top of the stepladder or if you cannot maintain a handhold on the ladder.
\n●	Maintain a firm grip. Use both hands when climbing.
\n\nWhen using a stepladder:
\n●	Do not overreach. Move a stepladder when needed.
\n●	Do not "shift" or "walk" a stepladder when standing on it.
\n●	Do not stand, climb, or sit on the stepladder top or pail shelf.
\n●	Do not overload. Stepladders are meant for one person.
\n●	Do not use a stepladder as a brace or as a support for a work platform or plank.

\n●	Do not climb a stepladder that is leaning against a wall. Use a straight ladder instead.
\n●	Do not use stepladders on slippery surfaces.
\n●	Do not use stepladders on soft ground where one leg may sink farther into the ground than others.
\n●	Do not place stepladders on boxes, unstable bases or on scaffolds to gain additional height.
\n●	Do not climb the back of a stepladder.
\n●	Do not push or pull stepladders sideways.
\n●	Do not use ladders in passageways, doorways, driveways or other locations where a person or vehicle can hit it. Set up suitable barriers or lock doors shut.
</item>
        <item>●	Place ladders on a firm, level surface and ensure the footing is secure.
\n●	Erect extension ladders so that the upper section rests on (e.g., in front of) the bottom section. This means the bottom section "faces" a wall or other supporting surface (see figures below).
\n●	Place the ladder feet so that the horizontal distance between the feet and the top support is 1/4 of the working length of the ladder. The ladder will be leaning at a 75 degree angle from the ground.

\n●	Raise and lower ladders from the ground. Ensure that locking ladder hooks are secure before climbing.
\n●	Erect ladders so that a minimum of 1 m (3 ft) extends above a landing platform. Tie the top at support points.
\n●	Brace or tie off the ladder near the base. If there is no structure to tie off to, use a stake in the ground.
\n●	Leave all tie-off devices in place until they must be removed before taking the ladder down.
\n●	Maintain the minimum overlap of sections as shown on a ladder label. Refer to safety regulations.
</item>
        <item>●	Check for overhead electrical wires before setting up a ladder.
\n●	Clear area around base and top of the ladder of debris, tools and other objects.
\n●	Tie off yourself with a safety harness when working 3 m (10 ft) or more off the ground or when working with both hands.
\n●	Ensure that only one person is on a single-width ladder. Only one person is allowed on each side of a double-width ladder.
\n●	Maintain three-point contact by keeping two hands and one foot, or two feet and one hand on the ladder at all times.
\n●	Grasp the rungs when climbing a ladder, not the side rails. If your foot slips on a ladder, holding onto rungs is easier than holding onto the side rails.

\n●	Wear protective footwear with slip-resistant soles and heels.
\n●	Ensure that all electrical equipment used during ladder work is in good condition and properly grounded.
\n●	Rest frequently to avoid arm fatigue and disorientation when the work requires you to look up and reach above your head.
\n●	Drape your arms over a rung and rest your head against another rung or side rail if you become dizzy or panicky. Climb down slowly.

</item>
        <item>An Extension Trestle Ladder requires level ground support for all four of its side rails. If this work site condition does not exist, an Extension Trestle Ladder should not be selected for the job.
\nAn Extension Trestle Ladder must not be used unless its base is spread fully open and the Spreaders locked. Extension Trestle Ladders are not to be used as Single Ladders or in the partially open position.
\nIn order to prevent tipping the ladder over sideways due to over-reaching, the user(s) must climb or work with the body near the middle of the steps or rungs. The ladder should be set-up close to the work. Never attempt to move the ladder without first descending, relocating the ladder, and then re-climbing. Do not attempt to mount the ladder from the side or step from one ladder to another unless the ladder is secured against sideways motion.

\nIn an effort to avoid losing your balance and falling off the Extension Trestle Ladder, the user must not step or stand higher than the step indicated on the label marking the highest standing level.
\nWhen ascending or descending the ladder, always face the ladder and maintain a firm hand hold. Do not attempt to carry other objects in your hand(s) while climbing.
\nThe anti-slip feet at the bottom of the base section side rails must be present and in good condition prior to using the ladder. The ladder must not be used on ice, snow or slippery surfaces unless suitable means to prevent slipping is employed.
\nAn Extension Trestle Ladder must never be placed upon other objects such as boxes, barrels, scaffolds, or other unstable bases in an effort to obtain additional height.
</item>
        <item>The Mobile Ladder Stand or Ladder Stand Platform manufacturer is required to provide maintenance instructions with each unit. These instructions must address visual inspection procedures, general maintenance, and proper tightening directions for threaded fasteners. Users are required to read and understand the user instructions before being allowed to use a Mobile Ladder Stand or Mobile Ladder Stand Platform. As an alternative, employers must instruct employees in the proper use of the units prior to allowing use.
\nUpon receipt following shipping and prior to each period of use, each Mobile Ladder Stand or Ladder Stand Platform unit must be visually inspected for damage, such as unusual wear, deterioration or corrosion. Any loose bolts, nuts or connections must be tightened. All threaded fasteners must be equipped with locking hardware. It is the owners’ responsibility to comply with the manufacturers’ maintenance instructions to maintain the quality and serviceability of the unit.
\nUnits that are damaged or weakened from any cause are not to be used until repairs are completed. Units that are damaged subsequent to their receipt and/or are worn beyond repair must be removed from service and destroyed.
\nGeneral maintenance of a Mobile Ladder Stand or Platform includes cleaning, lubrication, painting and the replacement of on-product labels and markings as well as wheels, casters and rubber pads.
\nClimbing a damaged Ladder Stand or Ladder Stand Platform is not permitted.
\nLadder Stands and Ladder Stand Platforms must never be moved while occupied.
\nUnits must not be loaded beyond their Rated Load capacity.
\nMaterials and/or equipment must not be stored on the Steps or Platform of a unit.
\nAdditional height must not be gained by the addition of any type of extension or object being placed upon the unit
</item>
        <item>A thorough inspection must be made when the ladder is initially purchased and each time it is placed into service. Clean the climbing and gripping surfaces if they have been subjected to oil, grease or slippery materials. Working parts, bolts, rivets, step-to-side rail connections, and the condition of the anti-slip feet (safety shoes) shall be checked.
\nLadders exposed to excessive heat, as in the case of fire, may have reduced strength. Similarly, ladders exposed to corrosive substances such as acids or alkali materials may experience chemical corrosion and a resulting reduction in strength. Remove these ladders from service.
\nBroken or bent ladders, and ladders with missing or worn out parts must be taken out of service and marked, for example, "Dangerous – Do Not Use” until repaired by a competent mechanic or destroyed. No attempt shall be made to repair a ladder with a defective side rail. Ladders with bent or broken side rails must be destroyed.
\nIn the event a ladder is discarded, it must be destroyed in such a manner as to render it useless. Another person must not be given the opportunity to use a ladder that has been deemed unsafe.
\nWhen transporting ladders on vehicles equipped with ladder racks, the ladders must be properly supported. Overhang of the ladders beyond the support points of the rack should be minimized. The support points should be constructed of material such as wood or rubber-covered pipe to minimize the effects of vibration, chafing and road shock. Securing the ladder to each support point will greatly reduce the damaging effects of road shock.
\nStorage racks for ladders not in use should have sufficient supporting points to avoid sagging which can result in warping the ladder. Other materials must not be placed on the ladder while it is in storage.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="respiratory_protection_howto">
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="scaffoldings_howto">
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
        <item>NOT YET AVAILABLE</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="fourth_how_to">
        <item>@array/aerial_lift_howto</item>
        <item>@array/crane_lift_howto</item>
        <item>@array/fire_sprinklers_howto</item>
        <item>@array/fork_lift_howto</item>
        <item>@array/heat_stress_howto</item>
        <item>@array/ladders_howto</item>
        <item>@array/respiratory_protection_howto</item>
        <item>@array/scaffoldings_howto</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="States">
        <item>Andhra Pradesh</item>
        <item>Delhi</item>
        <item>Gujarat</item>
        <item>Haryana</item>
        <item>Karnataka</item>
        <item>Kerala</item>
        <item>Maharashtra</item>
        <item>Orrisa</item>
        <item>Punjab</item>
        <item>Tamil Nadu</item>
        <item>Telangana</item>
        <item>West Bengal</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="AndhraPradeshLaws">
        <item>Factories Act</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="AndhraPradeshLawsImage">
        <item>@drawable/back_law7</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="AndhraPradeshforms">
    </string-array>
    <array name="AndhraPradesh">
        <item>@array/AndhraPradeshLaws</item>
        <item>@array/AndhraPradeshLawsImage</item>
        <item>@array/AndhraPradeshforms</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="DelhiLaws">
        <item>Fire Service Act</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="DelhiLawsImage">
        <item>@drawable/back_law1</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Delhiforms">
        <item>Record Lime Washing etc</item>
        <item>Over Time Muster Roll</item>
        <item>Notice Period for Adult Workers</item>
        <item>Register of Adult Workers</item>
        <item>Notice Period for Child Workers</item>
        <item>Register of Child Workers</item>
        <item>Register of Leave with Wages</item>
        <item>Health Register</item>
        <item>Annual Return</item>
        <item>Half yearly Retuns</item>
        <item>Muster Roll</item>
        <item>Register of Accident and Dangerous Occurrence</item>
        <item>Register of Trained Adult Workers</item>
        <item>Notice of Change of Mananger</item>
        <item>Register of Compensatory Holidays</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Delhi">
        <item>@array/DelhiLaws</item>
        <item>@array/DelhiLawsImage</item>
        <item>@array/Delhiforms</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="GujaratLaws">
        <item>Factories Act</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Gujaratimage">
        <item>@drawable/back_law3</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Gujaratform">
        <item>Overtime Register of Exempted Workers</item>
        <item>Register of Adult Workers</item>
        <item>Notice Period of Work for Child</item>
        <item>Register of Child Workers</item>
        <item>Register of Leave with Wages</item>
        <item>Notice of Change of Manager</item>
        <item>Record of Lime washing etc</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Gujarat">
        <item>@array/GujaratLaws</item>
        <item>@array/Gujaratimage</item>
        <item>@array/Gujaratform</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="HaryanaLaws">
        <item>Factories Rules</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="HaryanaImage">
        <item>@drawable/back_law2</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Haryanaform">
        <item>Record of Lime Washing etc</item>
        <item>Overtime Muster Roll for Exempted Worker</item>
        <item>Notice of Period for Adult Workers</item>
        <item>Register of Adult Workers</item>
        <item>Notice of Period for Child Workers</item>
        <item>Register of Child Workers</item>
        <item>Register of Leave with Wages</item>
        <item>Health Register</item>
        <item>Annual Return</item>
        <item>Half Yearly Return</item>
        <item>Muster Roll</item>
        <item>Register of Compensatory Holidays</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Haryana">
        <item>@array/HaryanaLaws</item>
        <item>@array/HaryanaImage</item>
        <item>@array/Haryanaform</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Karnatakalaws">
        <item>Citizen`s Charter</item>
        <item>Factories Act</item>
        <item>No Fees for Licence</item>
        <item>Factories Rules</item>
        <item>Fire Force Act</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Karnatakaimage">
        <item>@drawable/back_law3</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law4</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law5</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law6</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law7</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Karnatakaform">
        <item>Register of Accidents and Dangerous Occurrence</item>
        <item>Register of Adult workers</item>
        <item>Register of Leave with Wages</item>
        <item>Leave Book</item>
        <item>Health Register</item>
        <item>Factory Licence Renewal</item>
        <item>Annual Return</item>
        <item>Muster Roll</item>
        <item>Register of Overtime and Payment</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Karnataka">
        <item>@array/Karnatakalaws</item>
        <item>@array/Karnatakaimage</item>
        <item>@array/Karnatakaform</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Keralalaws">
        <item>Factories Rules</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Keralaimage">
        <item>@drawable/back_law7</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Keralaform">
    </string-array>
    <array name="Kerala">
        <item>@array/Keralalaws</item>
        <item>@array/Keralaimage</item>
        <item>@array/Keralaform</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Maharashtralaws">
        <item>Factories Act</item>
        <item>Labour Welfare Fund Act</item>
        <item>Fire Force Act</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Maharashtraimage">
        <item>@drawable/back_law1</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law2</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law3</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Maharashtraform">
        <item>Labour Welfare Board Cum Return</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Maharashtra">
        <item>@array/Maharashtralaws</item>
        <item>@array/Maharashtraimage</item>
        <item>@array/Maharashtraform</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Orrisalaws">
        <item>Factories Rules</item>
        <item>Holidays Act</item>
        <item>Fire Service Act</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Orrisaimage">
        <item>@drawable/back_law3</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law4</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law5</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Orrisaform">
    </string-array>
    <array name="Orrisa">
        <item>@array/Orrisalaws</item>
        <item>@array/Orrisaimage</item>
        <item>@array/Orrisaform</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Punjablaws">
        <item>Factories Rules</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Punjabimage">
        <item>@drawable/back_law5</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Punjabform">
        <item>Overtime Muster Roll for Exempted Worker</item>
        <item>Notice Period for Adult Workers</item>
        <item>Register of Adult Workers</item>
        <item>Notice Period for Child Workers</item>
        <item>Register of Child Workers</item>
        <item>Register of Leave with Wages</item>
        <item>Health Register</item>
        <item>Annual Returns</item>
        <item>Half Yearly Returns</item>
        <item>Muster Roll</item>
        <item>Record of Limewashing etc</item>
        <item>Register of Compensatory Holidays</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Punjab">
        <item>@array/Punjablaws</item>
        <item>@array/Punjabimage</item>
        <item>@array/Punjabform</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="TamilNadulaws">
        <item>Factories Act</item>
        <item>Factories Rules</item>
        <item>Fire Service Act</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="TamilNaduimage">
        <item>@drawable/back_law6</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law7</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law1</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="TamilNaduform">
    </string-array>
    <array name="TamilNadu">
        <item>@array/TamilNadulaws</item>
        <item>@array/TamilNaduimage</item>
        <item>@array/TamilNaduform</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Telanganalaws">
        <item>Factories Rules</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="TelanganaImage">
        <item>@drawable/back_law6</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="Telanganaform">
        <item>Register of Child Workers</item>
        <item>Factories Act Form</item>
        <item>Notice of Change of Manager</item>
        <item>Certificate of Fitness</item>
        <item>Annual Return</item>
        <item>Factories Rules and Forms</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Telangana">
        <item>@array/Telanganalaws</item>
        <item>@array/TelanganaImage</item>
        <item>@array/Telanganaform</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="WestBengallaws">
        <item>The Building and Other Workers Act</item>
        <item>The Manufacture Strorage and Import Rules</item>
        <item>Safety Officer Notification</item>
        <item>Factories Rules</item>
        <item>The Chemical Accidents Rules</item>
        <item>Fire Service Act</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="WestBengalimage">
        <item>@drawable/back_law1</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law2</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law3</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law4</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law5</item>
        <item>@drawable/back_law6</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="WestBengalform">

    </string-array>
    <array name="WestBengal">
        <item>@array/WestBengallaws</item>
        <item>@array/WestBengalimage</item>
        <item>@array/WestBengalform</item>
    </array>
    <array name="StatesLf">
        <item>@array/AndhraPradesh</item>
        <item>@array/Delhi</item>
        <item>@array/Gujarat</item>
        <item>@array/Haryana</item>
        <item>@array/Karnataka</item>
        <item>@array/Kerala</item>
        <item>@array/Maharashtra</item>
        <item>@array/Orrisa</item>
        <item>@array/Punjab</item>
        <item>@array/TamilNadu</item>
        <item>@array/Telangana</item>
        <item>@array/WestBengal</item>
    </array>

    <!--Youtube Links -->
    <array name="youtubeEmbed">
        <item>@array/aerial_lift_youtube</item>
        <item>@array/crane_lift_youtube</item>
        <item>@array/fire_sprinklers_youtube</item>
        <item>@array/fork_lift_youtube</item>
        <item>@array/heat_stress_youtube</item>
        <item>@array/ladders_youtube</item>
        <item>@array/respiratory_youtube</item>
        <item>@array/scaffolds_youtube</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="aerial_lift_youtube">
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OGZOX2f2Yrc</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/7j_q90XMqH0</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/M-mFITmJ_q4</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="crane_lift_youtube">
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OYO_w-eLfag</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/op8xvBmqQlU</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bQhkZVvd-IU</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/NDPUfTrp4IE</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/uO-RwTWqhrA</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jXIp0VEV67I</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/9u3EuI6JRQA</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/VWp9GOxrM08</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fire_sprinklers_youtube">
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0Ej2j6NuJdo</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ALUAHfU1nYg</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZDwRlcFl2Qo</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/uHIQwTmfA44</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fork_lift_youtube">
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/5zzPw_oe-So</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/pHcBUF5NzJ8</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/7s-h87pogc4</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tKw2numtNd8</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/qjZlFoKnyIw</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/PuHD3ZuxrWM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="heat_stress_youtube">
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ladders_youtube">
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tcsdVup8NzA</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sWuOBu3GjHw</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/jNggabGSvvs</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/isv6O-FIj8c</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/3g-Kwc7qMaY</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="respiratory_youtube">
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/0d_RaKdqeck</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/yBg2B2BP9nA</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/OJ3ANkCeSzE</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/EgtNgi7KMIk</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="scaffolds_youtube">
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/MFJ4FNy1qWU</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/56NZrk183BI</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hx9i3L2eDzs</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hx9i3L2eDzs</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hx9i3L2eDzs</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hx9i3L2eDzs</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hx9i3L2eDzs</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hx9i3L2eDzs</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hx9i3L2eDzs</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hx9i3L2eDzs</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
        <item>no</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Youtube Links END-->
</resources>